{
    "subject": "resource/Scoop_(2006_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Scarlett_Johansson",
    "human_readable": "Scoop (2006 film) stars Scarlett Johansson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9187482595443726,
            "question": "Who starred in the 2006 film Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.902238130569458,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Scarlett Johansson released in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7876891493797302,
            "question": "Are there any other actors in the film Scoop besides Scarlett Johansson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.785544216632843,
            "question": "Name a movie featuring Scarlett Johansson."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.77080899477005,
            "question": "Has Scarlett Johansson starred in other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7250298261642456,
            "question": "Is Scarlett Johansson an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5315696001052856,
            "question": "What year was the film Scoop released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4636456370353699,
            "question": "What genre is the film Scoop likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36379897594451904,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28917041420936584,
            "question": "What is the main character's profession in Scoop?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Scoop (2006 film) stars Scarlett Johansson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8274_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of Scoop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8274_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Scoop likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8274_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Scoop released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8274_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8274_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the answer to the query is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Scoop\" (2006 film) stars Scarlett Johansson as Sondra Pransky. This confirms that the triple is correct according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that the film \"Scoop\" from 2006 stars Scarlett Johansson, among other actors."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}